{
    "id": "yamamoo",
    "name": "Yamamoo",
    "yomi": "ヤマモー",
    "text": [
        "自称働く表現家。某物流企業で管理職として激務をこなしながら、いくつかのユニットやソロで日本各地だけでなく、海外でも公演経験あり。",
        "I am an employee and also an artist. I have experienced some expressions both with other people and by myself."
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Do you think expression is necessary?",
            "jp": "表現って必要？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "必要",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "必要ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "Do you often listen carefully?",
            "jp": "耳をそばだてる時ある？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Do you want someone to understand?",
            "jp": "理解してほしいと思う？",
            "yes": "Yse",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you often compare with someone?",
            "jp": "人と比べることある？",
            "yes": "Yes i do",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Do you like consuming?",
            "jp": "消費が好き？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "好きでない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you want to buy as much as you can at a 100 yen shop?",
            "jp": "いやというほど100均で買い物したい？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "してみたい",
            "no": "Not so much",
            "right": "別にしたくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Do you like young people these days?",
            "jp": "最近の若者は好き？",
            "yes": "Yes i like",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "嫌い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Did you feel good when you watched the TV program <b>Hanzawa Naoki</b>?",
            "jp": "半沢直樹見て、スッキリした？",
            "yes": "Yes i did",
            "left": "した",
            "no": "No i didn't / i never saw",
            "right": "してない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you want to travel abroad soon?",
            "jp": "早く海外旅行に行きたい？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "行きたい",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "行きたくない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Do you want to go and see this show?",
            "jp": "このイベント見てみたい？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "見たい",
            "no": "Not really",
            "right": "特に行きたいと思わない"
        }
    ]
}